Nícollas Isabel de Azevedo Manhães

Niterói, Brazil +55 (21) 99929-1990 / nicollasisabel@hotmail.com https://br.linkedin.com/in/nicollasisabel

Young, perspective, tenacious, enthusiastic and well-accomplished professional with 4+ years of experience in IT Industry, armed with broad-based background and skills in the areas of providing appropriate solution to business needs and problems. Training and display outstanding ability to plan, coordinate, implement practices and procedures to bring significant improvements in efficiency, productivity and technology processes, towards the successful attainment of organizational objectives and goals.

Programming skills

VB.Net | VB6 | VBA | C | Java | SQL | HTML | Javascript | CSS

Education

Pontifícia Universidade Católica do Rio de Janeiro (PUC-Rio)

2008-2014

BSc Computer Engineering

Universidade Federal Fluminense (UFF)

2015-2016

MBA Project Management

Experience

IT Analyst Ampla Aug 2014 - Present

- Working at MV Engineering board.
- Developing internal applications, aiming to help and organize the management of MV works, as well as periodic reports with the entire board KPIs, helping the Directors analyze and make decisions.
- From December 2015, was incorporated to the Remote Control Project Management team (MV network automation), which aims to raise the quality KPIs (Interruptions per consumer/Weighted Hours) as well as the quality of services offered to the clients, besides reducing the average time of maintenance and the cost of operation with the installation of 3.700 remote controlled equipments in the MV network, developing management reports and applications to help manage the project's completion and milestones.

Frontend Developer Intern Kendoo Solutions

Feb 2014 - Aug 2014

- Developed Android applications, using programming techniques, as clean code and code reuse.
- Frontend developer of WEB applications with strong usage of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery and Java, using Agile Project Management.



Backend Developer Intern Bank BBM

- Intern at Bank BBM, at IT applications Management board, improving and maintaining applications, as well as fixing bugs.
- Strong usage of VB.Net, SQL and VB6.

Languages

English:Portuguese:Spanish:IELTS General Test (CLB 7)NativeIntermediate

Volunteer experience

• TETO-Brasil 2014 - 2017

TETO-Brazil is a NGO that fight against the extreme poverty in Brazil. Present in more than 21 countries, promotes many events throughout the year. During house construction events, was the Head of Logistics, responsible to find the best cost-benefit supplier, organizing the arrival of materials, as well as finding the best route to distribute then inside the community.